Prey for Them
Wicked Little Things is a fantasy, horror film directed by J.S. Cardone.
Karen, Sarah, and Emma Tunney are all moving to a small town in Pennsylvania where, unknown to
them, in 1913, a horrid mine accident trapped dozens of children alive, underground.
But there's a problem.
They're still alive.
Karen Tunny, played by Lori Heuring.
Sarah Tunny, played by Scout Taylor-Compton.
Emma Tunny, played by Chloë Grace Moretz.
Harold Thompson, played by Geoffrey Lewis.
Aaron Hanks, played by Ben Cross.
Lisa, played by Julie Rogers.
Wicked Little Things (also known as Zombies) is a 2006
American zombie horror film directed by J.
Cardone and starring Lori Heuring, Scout Taylor-Compton and Chloë Grace Moretz.
The film was claimed to be based on true events.
The film explores themes of gallery, loss of loved one, mining accident, zombie.
The tone is dark and emotional.